A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Mary French Rockefeller papers FA1731
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Personal papers and Family Interests, 1918-1997; 2; 17.45 Cubic Feet 41 letter document boxes and 4 legal document boxes.
  - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Death - Sympathy Letters to Mary French Rockefeller, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Programs from Events, 1949-1991 (Box 117, Folder 3-4, Box 118, Folder 1-4, Box 119, Folder 1-2)
  - Vassar College, 1931-1992 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Africa Cooperative Action Trust (ACAT), 1990 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Atlanta University - Report of Growth 1865-1951 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Brearley School - House and Arts, 1949-1950 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Presentation of the Reception Wing of Gracie Mansion (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Rosemary Hall - Alumni Weekend, 1977 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Bethune Luncheon, 1991 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - New York Public Library - Annual Report, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund (RFF) - Report, 1995 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Contributions, 1965-1971 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Contributions, 1988-1990 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Contributions, 1991-1992, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Account No. 2 - N-Z, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Political Contributions, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - International Star Registry - LSR, 1988 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - New York Botanical Garden - Development and Program Plans, 1993-1999 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - LSR - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller: A Biography by Mary Ellen Chase, Good Housekeeping Magazine, 1950 June (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - LSR - A Brief History of the Union Church of Pocantico Hills, 1959 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    LSR copy? Duplicate.
  - LSR - Nelson A. Rockefeller Political Brochures (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - LSR - Standard Oil (of New Jersey) - Annual Report, 1949 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - LSR - United Nations News, 1949 November (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Contributions, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - YWCA - House Hearing, 1992 June 2 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Anniversary Card (Box 129, Folder 8)
    Oversized, computer-generated card.
  - Memoriam for Richard D. Vanderwarker (1911-1971) (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - The Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Memorial Window, Union Church of Pocantico Hills, 1959 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Family and Trip Photos (Box 130, Folder 1-2)
    Including MFR, LSR, and others.
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Election Pins (Plaque) (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - British Virgin islands First Day Cachets, 1973; Portfolio (Box 130, Folder 4)
- Art and Culture, 1953-1997; 3; 6.6 Cubic Feet 14 letter document boxes and 2 legal document boxes.
  - Berry School, 1966-1972 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Berry College - Upgrade Proposal, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Lila Acheson Wallace Wing, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art - Trustees, 1965, 1982-1988 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art - General, 1984-1987 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art - Corporate Campaign, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art - Education Committee Meeting, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Vermont Folklife Center - Minutes, Bylaws, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Young Concert Artists, Inc., 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Vassar College Art Gallery Plan, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 3, Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Vogue Magazine, 1968 May (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Vermont Folklife Center - Feasibility Study Report, 1993 April 15 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1980-1988 (Box 60, Folder 6-7)
    Includes capital campaign material, grant application, building program and planning study, and incorporation documents.
  - Excavations in Print, by Nancy Graves, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Book.
  - Billings Farm, 1953-1991 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Billings Mansion, 1954-1992 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Vermont Folklife Center, 1988-1989 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Princeton Art Museum, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Whitney Museum, 1966-1979 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Whitney Museum - Correspondence, 1965-1990 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Whitney Museum - Education Committee, 1976-1991 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Whitney Museum - Historic Art Committee, 1972-1979 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Woodstock Foundation, Inc., 1969-1987 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Woodstock Historical Society, 1965-1980 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Woodstock - History and Folklife, 1978 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Friends of the Whitney, 1970-1972 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Whitney Museum - Corporate Appeals, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Whitney Museum - Artreach, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - National Museum of the American Indian, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Whitney Museum, 1964-1996 (Box 124, Folder 1-2)
  - Vermont Land Trust, 1979-1987 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - "The Lady of the Eagle", Stone Artwork by Kathrin (Mrs. Walter) Hochschild (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Wildlife of the American West Art Museum - Appreciation Photo (Box 129, Folder 11)